Find the right song, change your past. Find the
right person, change your future.
The Greatest Hits is a drama, music, romance film directed by Ned Benson.
Harriet finds art imitating life when she discovers certain
songs can transport her back in time – literally.
While she relives the past through romantic memories of her former boyfriend, her time
travelling collides with a burgeoning new love interest in the present.
As she takes her journey through the hypnotic connection between music and
memory, she wonders – even if she could change the past, should she?
Harriet Gibbons, played by Lucy Boynton.
David Park, played by Justin H. Min.
Max Enders, played by David Corenswet.
Morris Martin, played by Austin Crute.
Dr. Evelyn Bartlett, played by Retta.
Edie Park, played by Andie Ju.
The Greatest Hits is a 2024 American romantic fantasy film written, produced
and directed by Ned Benson, and starring Lucy Boynton, Justin H.
Min, David Corenswet, and Austin Crute.
It follows Harriet (Boynton) who, mourning her deceased boyfriend, travels back in
time when she listens to a particular song associated with the latter.
Searchlight Pictures announced the film in August 2022, with principal
photography commencing at the end of the month and continued till October.
Much of the film was shot predominantly in Los Angeles
by cinematographer Chung-hoon Chung.
During post-production, the musical score was composed by Ryan
Lott and editing was completed by Saira Haider.
The Greatest Hits had its world premiere at South by Southwest on March 14, 2024 and had a limited theatrical
release on April 5, 2024, followed by a worldwide premiere as a Hulu original film on April 12, 2024.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of love triangle, time
travel, nostalgia, grief, healing.
The tone is emotional.